
<attribute>
    <name>src</name>
    <deferred-value>
        <type>java.lang.String</type>
    </deferred-value>
    <required>false</required>
    <rtexprvalue>false</rtexprvalue>
    <description><![CDATA[ SRC define the url of the required resource to load ]]>
    </description>
</attribute>

<attribute>
    <name>media</name>
    <deferred-value>
        <type>java.lang.String</type>
    </deferred-value>
    <required>false</required>
    <rtexprvalue>false</rtexprvalue>
    <description><![CDATA[ MEDIA define a media type for a Cascading Style Sheet.
    The names chosen for CSS media types reflect target devices for which the relevant properties make sense.
    In the following list of CSS media types the names of media types are normative, but the descriptions are informative.
    Likewise, the "Media" field in the description of each property is informative.
    <ul>
    <li>all : Suitable for all devices.</li>
    <li>braille : Intended for braille tactile feedback devices.</li>
    <li>embossed : Intended for paged braille printers.</li>
    <li>handheld : Intended for handheld devices (typically small screen, limited bandwidth).</li>
    <li>print : Intended for paged material and for documents viewed on screen in print preview mode.
    Please consult the section on paged media for information about formatting issues that are specific to paged media.</li>
    <li>projection : Intended for projected presentations, for example projectors.
    Please consult the section on paged media for information about formatting issues that are specific to paged media.</li>
    <li>screen : Intended primarily for color computer screens.</li>
    <li>speech : Intended for speech synthesizers. Note: CSS2 had a similar media type called 'aural' for this purpose.
    See the appendix on aural style sheets for details.</li>
    <li>tty : Intended for media using a fixed-pitch character grid (such as teletypes, terminals, or portable devices with limited display capabilities).
    Authors should not use pixel units with the "tty" media type.</li>
    <li>tv : Intended for television-type devices (low resolution, color, limited-scrollability screens, sound available).</li>
    </ul>]]>
    </description>
</attribute>