
<attribute>
    <name>dir</name>
    <deferred-value>
        <type>boolean</type>
    </deferred-value>
    <required>false</required>
    <rtexprvalue>false</rtexprvalue>
    <description><![CDATA[This attribute specifies the base direction of directionally neutral text
    (i.e., text that doesn't have inherent directionality as defined in [UNICODE]) in an element's content and attribute values.
    It also specifies the directionality of tables. Possible values:
    <ul>
    <li>if this attribute is FALSE = LTR: Left-to-right text or table.</li>
    <li>if this attribute is TRUE  = RTL: Right-to-left text or table.</li>
    </ul>]]>
    </description>
</attribute>

<attribute>
    <name>lang</name>
    <deferred-value>
        <type>java.lang.String</type>
    </deferred-value>
    <required>false</required>
    <rtexprvalue>false</rtexprvalue>
    <description><![CDATA[This attribute specifies the base language of an element's attribute values and text content.
    The default value of this attribute is unknown.
    Language information specified via the lang attribute may be used by a user agent to control rendering in a variety of ways.
    Some situations where author-supplied language information may be helpful include:
    <ul>
    <li>Assisting search engines</li>
    <li>Assisting speech synthesizers</li>
    <li>Helping a user agent select glyph variants for high quality typography</li>
    <li>Helping a user agent choose a set of quotation marks</li>
    <li>Helping a user agent make decisions about hyphenation, ligatures, and spacing</li>
    <li>Assisting spell checkers and grammar checkers</li>
    </ul>
    The lang attribute specifies the language of element content and attribute values;
    whether it is relevant for a given attribute depends on the syntax and semantics of the attribute and the operation involved.
    The intent of the lang attribute is to allow user agents to render content more meaningfully based on accepted cultural practice for a given language.
    This does not imply that user agents should render characters that are atypical for a particular language in less meaningful ways;
    user agents must make a best attempt to render all characters, regardless of the value specified by lang.]]>
    </description>
</attribute>

<attribute>
    <name>profile</name>
    <deferred-value>
        <type>java.lang.String</type>
    </deferred-value>
    <required>false</required>
    <rtexprvalue>false</rtexprvalue>
    <description><![CDATA[This attribute specifies the location of one or more meta data profiles, separated by white space.
    For future extensions, user agents should consider the value to be a list even though this specification only considers the first URI to be significant.
    Profiles are discussed below in the section on meta data.]]>
    </description>
</attribute>

<attribute>
    <name>title</name>
    <deferred-value>
        <type>java.lang.String</type>
    </deferred-value>
    <required>false</required>
    <rtexprvalue>false</rtexprvalue>
    <description><![CDATA[Every HTML document must have a TITLE element in the HEAD section.
    Authors should use the TITLE element to identify the contents of a document.
    Since users often consult documents out of context, authors should provide context-rich titles.
    Thus, instead of a title such as "Introduction", which doesn't provide much contextual background,
    authors should supply a title such as "Introduction to Medieval Bee-Keeping" instead.]]>
    </description>
</attribute>